Register of the James Burnham Papers, 1928-1983
Hoover Institution Archives
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, 1943-1969.
  - 2 prints of Czech students carrying a wreath in the funeral procession of Jan Palach, 1969; 4 prints of a villa in Greece (?), undated; 5 prints of Suzette and Enrique Ellinger, 1943; 1 print of Mrs. Burnham(?), undated; 1 group photograph from the Public Affairs Conference on Foreign Aid, January 1962 (Folder 10.A-V)